{
    "id": "cdedaa3c4fdd4188b975dc60e5738da7",
    "title": "Question Tags Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You are the new secretary, ………………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are you",
                "aren't you",
                "were you"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "The meeting is at four o’clock, ………………………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is it",
                "isn't it",
                "has it"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You didn’t meet him, ……………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "didn't you",
                "did you"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You like flowers, ………………………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do you",
                "don't you"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "You haven’t seen my keys, ……………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have you",
                "haven't you",
                "had you"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Harry gave you a gift, ………………………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does he",
                "did he",
                "didn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s have a party, ……………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shall we",
                "can we",
                "should we"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "There aren’t any problems, ……………………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are there",
                "aren't there",
                "don't there"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "Nothing can happen, ……………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can nothing",
                "can it",
                "can't it"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody phoned, ………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did they",
                "didn't they",
                "had they"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}